{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"ee480acf-a32d-4435-86cd-907de2bcfad0"},"exam":{"id":"ee46df02-7b41-4129-8230-84363a5b9da8","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"rv438cbg-ow9h-jrfd-gxxt-a83ko2ojlo7c","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS' Global Infrastructure, what are Edge Locations responsible for?","explanation":"Edge Locations host a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"0df5575df91cfdc3471135f97cd57b5b","text":"Providing redundant backup to your AWS services","correct":false},{"id":"7e293752730d983b3fb263bc37525a5c","text":"Hosting a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"e2dd2357c3f760b6df8cd9ef82402a0e","text":"Providing disaster recovery services","correct":false},{"id":"3d5bde6fd721f0872d6ad91a83e073cd","text":"Providing independent power grids to Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"gz05o0zm-686t-arfr-tr1s-7wjbwyv832dv","domain":"tech","question":"You need to allow resources in a private subnet to access the internet. Which of the following must be present to enable this access?","explanation":"A NAT Gateway is required to allow resources in a private subnet to access the internet. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, but don't actually process or transmit traffic. Security Groups and Network Access Control Lists are used to protect resources from traffic, and by themselves do not enable access to the internet - although they need to be properly configured to let traffic bound for the internet out.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/vpc-nat-gateway.html","title":"About NAT Gateways"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"8ca0f1328403ec0d05ed995272d74715","text":"NAT Gateway","correct":true},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they don’t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false},{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false},{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false},{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false},{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true}]},{"id":"35f041db-16e3-4bb3-825d-7ab528bddd1b","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following falls under AWS compute services category?","explanation":"EC2, Lightsail, and Elastic Beanstalk fall under the compute umbrella of AWS services. EFS and AWS Backup are classified as storage services, and Amazon RDS is classified as database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"ce1a41ee0352cee512475ef6a6233963","text":"Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)","correct":true},{"id":"d2a6652ddeb631da029d1f2806e11fdc","text":"Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)","correct":false},{"id":"98492fcf8e38ae7ea331e271498d5275","text":"Amazon Relational Database Services (RDS)","correct":false},{"id":"9e10649cd5a6507c47e44a66dc03eb5b","text":"Amazon Lightsail","correct":true},{"id":"ce52d2cff6e50f2e74505e0c70d072b3","text":"AWS Backup","correct":false},{"id":"765c63bdfc41e7ae2614191faa2b0d0a","text":"Amazon Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true}]},{"id":"uqrnb9d8-haf3-bm5v-dcoo-t32fx6qgqhwi","domain":"tech","question":"Your application needs a MySQL database, but you need better performance than you could get running MySQL on EC2. Which of the following AWS services should you consider?","explanation":"Aurora is AWS' managed MySQL database. It delivers up to 5X the performance of a MySQL database running on EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/","title":"About Aurora"}],"answers":[{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"509e0895bd82e3315e79018a6ce02181","text":"Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"f8d3b65d8479a31ebf67cb18dd0a4641","text":"Neptune","correct":false},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false}]},{"id":"ff57921e-2faa-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"All statements listed here are correct except for one. If you don’t use all your Free Tier benefits within the month, they don’t roll over to the next month.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-free-tier.html","title":"Using the AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"e0a5844f80154f67479f312499e75d1a","text":"Usage must be kept below the Free Tier limits to avoid charges.","correct":true},{"id":"aec630c6387bfee54b18d0ca80ea994c","text":"Unused benefits that the Free Tier provides in a given month roll over to the next month.","correct":false},{"id":"fca0d4d0e7ba8ff0a86efa806423c98d","text":"AWS starts charging the regular rates for usage of services and resources when the Free Tier expires.","correct":true},{"id":"8723f65debe98902ae71daeac7ca33e0","text":"Upon creation of an AWS account, the user is automatically signed up for the Free Tier for 12 months.","correct":true}]},{"id":"e3b24121-862f-4b1e-8f4e-18e6f3f9e1e8","domain":"concepts","question":"VMware Cloud on AWS allows companies to migrate and extend their on-premises VMware vSphere-based environments to AWS Cloud using Amazon EC2. Which of the following choices accurately classifies this deployment model?","explanation":"Hybrid deployments connect infrastructure and applications between cloud-based resources and existing resources that are not located in the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is an example of a hybrid deployment, since it involves the on-premises environments of VMware and the cloud-based services of AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","title":"Hybrid Cloud with AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"c8e2277ecfb1427838c488c217f99466","text":"Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"fb1b6e23a3767d2a31ef7899e6dd3f1e","text":"Hybrid","correct":true},{"id":"0fca8d17afc46bb08bd2d70a26cdf886","text":"On-Premises","correct":false},{"id":"d6eb128e4c8971dc397f021585391999","text":"Shared Services","correct":false}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"bccfe3b0-61d9-4680-81cc-45a78d8a722d","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following options are available for configuring a password policy for IAM users of an AWS account?","explanation":"The password policy options does not include the requirement of using at least one numerical character from 1 to 9; it is actually at least one numerical character from 0 to 9. Passwords can contain between 6 to 128 characters, so 12 to 64 characters is incorrect. The other three options listed are correct.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"454e4156bef76a1758de1fb18c771f5b","text":"Require that passwords contain at least one of the AWS-listed nonalphanumeric characters.","correct":true},{"id":"9fd02d6b80fbf23454be435b3ecbe598","text":"Use between 6 to 128 characters to form the password.","correct":true},{"id":"fcce064756de55a96a60925043d2feb0","text":"Use between 12 to 64 characters to form the password.","correct":false},{"id":"7115f92e53f08f3e583dcfde0a88161b","text":"Use at least one numerical character from 1 to 9.","correct":false},{"id":"164affd52e9cf98d09976ffa798d82dd","text":"Allow users to change their passwords.","correct":true}]},{"id":"96g9onz0-tv5t-sedb-7kg9-wv5k4uz50hgn","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWS' Data Warehousing service?","explanation":"Redshift is AWS' data warehousing service. Elastic Map Reduce is a large scale data processing service. Snowball is a physical appliance used to transfer data into, or out of AWS. S3 Big Data does not exist.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon Redshift?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c0429b6a658dd488f7262d983c7e02bb","text":"Snowball","correct":false},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":true},{"id":"6d5e386be8e0c962fec3431ac8198e82","text":"S3 Big Data","correct":false},{"id":"22ab04a992dc8483216fed8f9b932b77","text":"Elastic Map Reduce","correct":false}]},{"id":"xun4oj55-ptum-ekl7-y5ot-pqhc5t5psvxi","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following support plans features unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases?","explanation":"Both Enterprise and Business support plans feature unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true}]},{"id":"evaz1xrv-t8dc-4b8o-0z8b-k29mzh203trs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers the assistance of a Technical Account Manager?","explanation":"Only Enterprise (the highest level of Support Plan) offers the services of a Technical Account Manager.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"8d5e7e72f12067991186cdf3cb7d5d9d","text":"Premium","correct":false}]},{"id":"00f56002-e145-4ed1-94f4-c041d0edd78f","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is a correct S3 bucket name?","explanation":"Bucket names must start with a lowercase letter or number and must not contain uppercase characters or underscores. 2nd-headquarters-imgs is the only bucket name listed here that adheres to these rules and restrictions.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev//BucketRestrictions.html#bucketnamingrules","title":"Rules for Bucket Naming"}],"answers":[{"id":"5d54f4723cb2118e1da2a67a7628f77d","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2nd_Headquarters_imgs","correct":false},{"id":"50ccd1e352082b9d31184e260c3830ef","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/Second-headquarters-imgs","correct":false},{"id":"2b56c4f3ee0c03e44e37656e651fafcf","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2nd-headquarters-imgs","correct":true},{"id":"5457bb8e9a20209e28f939482cbf590c","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/Headquartersimg","correct":false}]},{"id":"768b0aa8-1fea-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon S3 Standard storage will you get for no cost?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 5 GB of standard S3 storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":true},{"id":"b3dd42c7956751be5d38b5c0cb2e09c0","text":"5 TB","correct":false},{"id":"0d642755e7f12f7563e3db33bd0c39cb","text":"1 GB","correct":false},{"id":"3a6d03856b824be771cdd922375d59db","text":"20 GB","correct":false},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false}]},{"id":"89c58d68-554a-45ea-9da8-fcf90103d4e8","domain":"concepts","question":"The Chief Marketing Officer of the hotel chain you work for would like to implement voice recognition capabilities in rooms so customers can request services without picking up the phone. Competitors have already begun rolling out these technologies in an attempt to improve their customers’ experience. Which benefit of the AWS cloud would you most emphasize to the CMO in your business case for creating an AWS-based solution?","explanation":"The AWS cloud provides instant access to new technologies. Companies can move with agility to satisfy new business requirements and meet competitive demands. There is a very low barrier of entry for innovation. If a solution is not meeting expectations, services can be instantly de-provisioned. The other three options will also prove to be benefits of deploying in the AWS cloud, but the use case emphasizes the need to move quickly against competitive threats.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"241bb470b0110efc8b5609f7311b0bb1","text":"Agility","correct":true},{"id":"ecbe6eb71bcb646d89d2e361dfa84c21","text":"Cost Savings","correct":false},{"id":"6cdf2174e24cf3e60f016e85f00c34ff","text":"Deploy Globally in Minutes","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"ybx4uf1a-l9y3-aucn-tt1m-ku92d3hu5y5v","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are configuratble components of IAM?","explanation":"Users, Groups, Roles, and Permissions are integral to IAM. Authentication and Authorization are functions that IAM provides, but not actual components of it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/getting-started/","title":"IAM - Getting Started"}],"answers":[{"id":"2999b7d01e6b02e94fc22c79b978d3b0","text":"Access controls","correct":false},{"id":"3948d67c633d9035eaf2216ba0e1b2dc","text":"Authenticator","correct":false},{"id":"a5cd3ed116608dac017f14c046ea56bf","text":"Roles","correct":true},{"id":"18ade94f5fe966167a6645362290cdcb","text":"Authorizer","correct":false},{"id":"f9aae5fda8d810a29f12d1e61b4ab25f","text":"Users","correct":true},{"id":"d08ccf52b4cdd08e41cfb99ec42e0b29","text":"Permissions","correct":true},{"id":"a37ede293936e29279ed543129451ec3","text":"Groups","correct":true}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false},{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true},{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false},{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true}]},{"id":"84d8ac20-2fb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Once you exceed a usage percentage of Free Tier limits for any service, AWS will automatically send you an email notification. What is that percentage?","explanation":"If you exceed 85% of Free Tier usage, AWS will automatically send you an email to notify you. This is to alert you to help with staying within the Free Tier limits; otherwise, you may incur charges.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"3ef815416f775098fe977004015c6193","text":"85","correct":true},{"id":"d09bf41544a3365a46c9077ebb5e35c3","text":"75","correct":false},{"id":"c0c7c76d30bd3dcaefc96f40275bdc0a","text":"50","correct":false},{"id":"1c383cd30b7c298ab50293adfecb7b18","text":"35","correct":false}]},{"id":"a392d2dd-28e1-4e5d-8a64-6a84e5e3f3e8","domain":"tech","question":"Which Elastic Load Balancer type would be best suited to help you host a website?","explanation":"Although it looks like the right answer - there is no \"Web\" load balancer in AWS. Instead, the Application Load Balancer fills this need. It is not recommended to use Classic Load Balancers anymore are these have been superseded, and a network Load Balancer is not right for this case.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/","title":"Elastic Load Balancing"}],"answers":[{"id":"d35b51b639528d580362ca7042de6a0e","text":"Classic","correct":false},{"id":"eec89088ee408b80387155272b113256","text":"Network","correct":false},{"id":"e498749f3c42246d50b15c81c101d988","text":"Application","correct":true},{"id":"c6e190b284633c48e39e55049da3cce8","text":"Web","correct":false}]},{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false},{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true},{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false},{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false}]},{"id":"prqyybkg-4flz-vdjf-hmny-u1q34ck87hm9","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are AWS compute services?","explanation":"EC2 and Lambda are AWS Compute Services, while RDS is a Database service, and SNS is an Application Integration service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/compute/","title":"AWS Compute"}],"answers":[{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"54afc4697cf03d8e3ec9a05b16380622","text":"SNS","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":true}]},{"id":"332dccb8-1a46-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following CIDR block size ranges applies to IPv4 addresses in Amazon VPC?","explanation":"For IPv4 addresses, the VPC CIDR block size can be anywhere from /16 to /28.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/vpc-ip-addressing.html","title":"IP Addressing in Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"d312bf1a99a33142c6a946375494aa20","text":"/12 to /32","correct":false},{"id":"699292f46538d2bf62bace8334097bb6","text":"1/ to /40","correct":false},{"id":"30575066a7baaedf5c35a22bc44a6964","text":"/16 to /28","correct":true},{"id":"b23abf46c1e7e117251291617bac5c56","text":"/8 to /36","correct":false}]},{"id":"d29bb03a-1a55-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for? (Choose 3)","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services. Such services include Amazon VPC, which enables a customer to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud. This section is simply referred to as a virtual private cloud, or VPC. So, while AWS is responsible for the software (Amazon VPC), the customer is responsible for the virtual network created with that software (VPC), as well as whatever goes in it. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses) and security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"452be8d0a4b871d9b4ec8f7e323a17a2","text":"Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)","correct":true},{"id":"1d7c6a62b7a045346e19186c911b38a1","text":"Amazon VPC Service","correct":false},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true}]},{"id":"c3f7fb72-1aba-4b4a-a88d-ab28709130ae","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following services are available 24x7 for all AWS Support Plans?","explanation":"All AWS Support plans provide 24x7 access to customer service, documentation, and support forums. For 24x7 access to Cloud Support Engineers, you will specifically need to get a Business or Enterprise Support plan.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a42a69de8cb0bc12c105962bb2df8561","text":"Support forums","correct":true},{"id":"ba4ffb983499bcebaa93c87030f33728","text":"Cloud Support Engineers","correct":false},{"id":"2273d1167a6212812d95dc8fadbae78e","text":"Customer service","correct":true},{"id":"df710f89ebb9e663bd3d66607a0bf413","text":"AWS documentation","correct":true}]},{"id":"czniv95k-ni5r-uuf9-ndk0-hf5pnoza8yy9","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is a fast, fully managed data warehouse that makes it simple and cost-effective to analyze all your data using standard SQL and your existing Business Intelligence tools.","explanation":"Redshift is AWS' fully-managed data warehouse solution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/","title":"About Redshift"}],"answers":[{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"22ab04a992dc8483216fed8f9b932b77","text":"Elastic Map Reduce","correct":false},{"id":"594025cae6dfa6b9073dc25de93ddb56","text":"Kinesis","correct":false}]},{"id":"e64254c2-1a50-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services, which includes Amazon VPC. By comparison, the customer is responsible for what goes in the AWS Cloud. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses), security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic), and network ACLs as additional layers of security.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"3ca98dadd6a9bcbe75450331cd449df5","text":"Network access control lists (network ACLs)","correct":true},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"97fd1873341a4d886cd8a23614cef0ff","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"b9e84187-a101-b202-89a5-c5882d80f712","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Patch Management is a Shared Control, since AWS is responsible for patching and fixing flaws within the infrastructure, including managed services like RDS, but customers are responsible for patching their guest OS and applications. Firmware Upgrades, and other Hardware maintenance processes are solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of Security Groups remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"c57c1a92dac4991db4fa1bca1517cca0","text":"Hardware Maintanence","correct":false},{"id":"5d8e5aef41d3dab7bda43eaace3a2a06","text":"Patch Management","correct":true},{"id":"474eabe8590389108f1fc92c9435c405","text":"Security Group Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"9ce46290f3196adff1535137f5fc1ee9","text":"Firmware Upgrades","correct":false}]},{"id":"71sehgn8-lx4k-034j-srs9-vv6xhd7w10qh","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to performance efficiency?","explanation":"Of these choices, you should democratize advanced technologies, deploy into multiple Regions, and use Serverless technologies.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"8c3a4b8048462b1877e2da598308fe3a","text":"Democratize advanced technologies.","correct":true},{"id":"db3e408a0aa09a4e83bdace8a1e57fcc","text":"Deploy into multiple Regions to go global in minutes.","correct":true},{"id":"56110ec02fe5d9a3ae8e5a69af838158","text":"Have your IT staff master all new technologies.","correct":false},{"id":"e891a453952de1898dde71f36801790a","text":"Use Serverless architectures.","correct":true},{"id":"c25dea02447eef08ddb2affdbb171485","text":"Mechanical empathy","correct":false}]},{"id":"ej2zjxm0-a6xk-q2af-mol8-3c9zwje8qxyh","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans features a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system?","explanation":"Both the Business and Enterprise support levels offer a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system. Developer is < 12-hour response time in case of any system impairment. Basic does not offer any support for system impairment. Individual is not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]},{"id":"npfixa13-rww8-6ifs-mar3-1z12ny6vwzat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following services will help you optimize your entire AWS environment in real-time following AWS best practices?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor helps you optimize your entire AWS environment in real-time following AWS best practices. It helps you optimize cost, fault-tolerance, and more.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false}]},{"id":"cfea2363-9af8-4536-b812-8ea53c44b11b","domain":"security","question":"You just had a Data Analyst join the company, and you have been tasked with creating a new IAM user accordingly. Although the user has received all the necessary credentials, she realized that she cannot perform any Amazon RDS actions on the Clients table. Which of the following are possible solutions to this issue?","explanation":"By default, an IAM user can’t access anything in the AWS account. So, the inability to perform the RDS actions on the Clients table is not a technical or password issue. To grant the permission to do so, you would need to create an identity-based policy. However, if there is a group in the account with the permission policy that will grant such access, you can add the user to that group instead.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_access-management.html","title":"Overview of Access Management: Permissions and Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"94412f8679d11dc0613f571ca4fba16b","text":"Add the user to the group that has the necessary permissions policy.","correct":true},{"id":"f46d75eb223838121ca6bec9ca08eaaa","text":"Create a ticket for the Help Desk to resolve the issue.","correct":false},{"id":"1971cb80efb016ad4254e3847a847434","text":"Supply the password necessary to log into the AWS console.","correct":false},{"id":"7731c1bfd28c89eee71012d973fa5407","text":"Double-check the credentials you sent to the user.","correct":false},{"id":"2f96bead1d7909e64836767c4e098acd","text":"Create an identity-based policy.","correct":true}]},{"id":"g7u8frqb-st05-cduw-gbms-boj1g5a4xb99","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below best describes DynamoDB?","explanation":"DynamoDB is a fast and flexible NoSQL database. NoSQL databases are non-relational, and have a dynamic structure, whereas SQL is relational and has a pre-defined structure. MySQL is a type of SQL database and Mongo is a type of NoSQL database, but neither of these are DynamoDB. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/","title":"DynamoDB"}],"answers":[{"id":"30baf17e85e225ed9bb718ded752d263","text":"DynamoDB is a an SQL database","correct":false},{"id":"bbd2da8aa588d6741d84847621ad4503","text":"DynamoDB is a Mongo database","correct":false},{"id":"f311f0c1ec783313330a4fd83fbb6200","text":"DynamoDB is a NoSQL database","correct":true},{"id":"482666cddcef688e890d4b901ebf8a32","text":"DynamoDB is a MySQL database","correct":false}]},{"id":"2df4774c-2e69-4156-96c5-b1efbfba754f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. This means there will always be more AZs than Regions. Edge locations are separate from AZs and Regions, and there are more Edge Locations than Regions and Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"f4b49cc5b3d286cd78cac99f03cecce3","text":"There are more Regions than Availability zones","correct":false},{"id":"f35fa3c5e765907efd6efa66bc1741c3","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"26c658a3c4aee0122f0178a65f0ea80b","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Regions","correct":true},{"id":"29030db1d3f86fea8d8779a9c964c207","text":"There are more Availability Zones than Edge locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"porkjt4t-1idl-7vgv-mx2b-s6gvayouwvh4","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are advantages of cloud computing?","explanation":"Elasticity, Agility, and the ability to control the variances in your month-to-month expenditure are all advantages of the flexibility of Cloud Computing. You do still need specialist knowledge to deploy solutions in the Cloud, such as AWS Certifications. Large amounts of capital are also not needed due to the consumption model of most cloud services, although you can sometimes use capital expenditure to purchase resources for extended periods of time, such as Reserved Instances in EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0368a69e2586f302d0f3da6bfa3b031","text":"Agility - Decreasing the time to start new services","correct":true},{"id":"b6244c70b8f2eb23f7eb82a740202646","text":"No specialist knowledge required","correct":false},{"id":"97e11cb086bf1070777e7e3fa1e31877","text":"Requires large amounts of capital","correct":false},{"id":"230dee0a7da58ba8fbf9dee4e7448de2","text":"Elasticity - you need not worry about capacity.","correct":true},{"id":"e614fc350d8c3730eaca43265d43d9de","text":"Variable expense","correct":true}]},{"id":"rc4dwp79-ix5s-h912-sdcj-9gmmhl6zacte","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed DDoS protection service?","explanation":"AWS Shield is AWS' managed DDoS protection service at Layer 4. AWS WAF provides protection from common exploits against your web applications at Layer 7, and does not protect against DDoS attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/?nc2=h_l3_dm","title":"About AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true}]},{"id":"2o4xzter-rc6s-wz14-cd0x-5ymcmahyoj0q","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an EC2 instance on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, EC2 patching is a Shared Control - AWS is responsible for the underlying hardware, but you as the user is responsible for patching the OS and Applications running in your instance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"92d4ae83f773c1e79ec7ae29b20fa481","text":"Patching the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"b8a5da87a2cdeca59f9782e25182f574","text":"Patching the applications","correct":true},{"id":"ce74e3a1c22bccb58acc0062f43153bd","text":"Patching the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"3e164c265c82649647e641e322d93aa7","text":"Patching the operating system","correct":true}]},{"id":"o8aqfsp4-kk6k-gyj7-frq7-4bpn7iv5zqm8","domain":"concepts","question":"You have a mission-critical application which must be globally available at all times. Which deployment strategy should you follow?","explanation":"A Multi-Region deployment will best ensure global availability. While it can be the most expensive, and complex to configure, Multi-Regional architectures will ensure that even if all Availability Zones in a single region fail due to a catastrophic event, your data will remain accessible.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"e4ec2833a31f482abfdb31691f0351dc","text":"Multi-Region","correct":true},{"id":"ec206762c0bea997a5b0f91783cce54f","text":"Multi-Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"91d7ff212b9bda483701aeb4209ae5ec","text":"Deploy to all Availability Zones in your home region.","correct":false},{"id":"86b2c5243e03e210528f020bad4efdb9","text":"Multi-VPC in two AWS Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"pzjuwu91-24rb-x77o-tzlj-dzpn3pvo3v3v","domain":"security","question":"You need to use an AWS service to assess the security and compliance of your EC2 instances. Which of the following services should you use?","explanation":"AWS Inspector is an automated security assessment service that helps improve the security and compliance of applications deployed on AWS. AWS Trusted Advisor can give security recommendations about your AWS resources, but not within EC2 instances themselves. AWS Shield and WAF can protect EC2 instances, but don't possess any capabilities to assess their security and compliance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/?nc2=h_m1","title":"About AWS Inspector"}],"answers":[{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false}]},{"id":"jpt9cxq0-nxn2-jxb3-g66u-ucfgv69ofwnu","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are key components of Amazon Glacier?","explanation":"Data is organised in S3 into Archives, and Vaults are used to group Archives together. Access policies control who can access the data in Archives & Vaults. Buckets are a part of S3, but not Glacier. Volumes are often associated with hard disks and therefore EBS, while Tables are database constructs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/","title":"About Glacier"}],"answers":[{"id":"51c45b795d5d18a3e4e0c37e8b20a141","text":"Table","correct":false},{"id":"bd7a9717d29c5ddcab1bc175eda1e298","text":"Volume","correct":false},{"id":"5b70a213f150f01f0776fa9481ef2ddf","text":"Vault","correct":true},{"id":"e727b00944f81e1d0a95c12886ac4641","text":"Archive","correct":true},{"id":"30edf70db68aa84f05d3e72326807b0c","text":"Bucket","correct":false},{"id":"8e2ddf5878aac8b5d22a6acab856040d","text":"Access Policy","correct":true}]},{"id":"p591e7kl-wfkp-78wh-zz8y-kf2mmf34gdw1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are steps you should take in securing your AWS account?","explanation":"The Root account should have MFA enabled, due to it's unlimited access to an account. You should always create IAM users for individual users, since the Root account should never be used for actual work. Groups should be used to delegate permissions to the users you create, instead of individual assigning policies to IAM users since it makes administration easier. Assigning policies directly to any user is not a good idea, since it can be hard to figure out who has access to what resources with many users.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","title":"IAM best practice"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_create_for-user.html","title":"IAM using Roles"}],"answers":[{"id":"8ef2b84b0ea8ddc5ae686a44387d63d7","text":"Activate Multi-factor Authentication (MFA) on your root account.","correct":true},{"id":"2e679971f295b42ffb5f0228883437fb","text":"Use groups to delegate access to IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"bd3cf659e9d378f1808cdb33b54baa84","text":"Assign policies directly to your administrative users","correct":false},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true}]},{"id":"t9dm8phv-f52w-bfsh-qrp9-6p8yl3d9o992","domain":"tech","question":"For a subnet to be public and send non-local traffic to the Internet, we must update the Route Table of the public subnet and attach which of the following to the VPC that contains the subnet?","explanation":"An Internet Gateway enables resources inside you VPC to reach the internet, as long as route tables and IP addresses are correctly configured in your environment.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Internet_Gateway.html","title":"About Internet Gateways"}],"answers":[{"id":"3fdc04800c36e2177d81c4431616f533","text":"Internet Gateway","correct":true},{"id":"c8525a9dfff01ff2bc0d471627bc0708","text":"Network Access Control List","correct":false},{"id":"8ca0f1328403ec0d05ed995272d74715","text":"NAT Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"0893147538c21c827dc499b4852934e3","text":"Route 53","correct":false}]},{"id":"c6jepoji-nqyo-0t96-juj8-ob2lymloevj9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Assurance Program?","explanation":"Certifications/Attestations and Compliance with Laws and Regulations are cornerstones of the of the AWS Assurance Program.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Assurance"}],"answers":[{"id":"fc0d934854b825185d4ea2079edf68c3","text":"Compliance with Laws and Regulations","correct":true},{"id":"de208db5a32df9befe2ed7f080863f9e","text":"Customer Testimonials","correct":false},{"id":"4dc626268903b46b79d0a76e0a989cf8","text":"Partner Validations","correct":false},{"id":"19d78b92947f957cca4c7698118fdb82","text":"Following industry best practices","correct":false},{"id":"506afacef0a47cc7635b5cf0a3476c31","text":"Certifications/Attestations","correct":true}]},{"id":"d05a0228-8d82-4cef-8dfb-4e2cb3856a9f","domain":"security","question":"According to the Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is AWS responsible for?","explanation":"Protecting the infrastructure that runs all of the services in the AWS Cloud is the responsibility of AWS. Such services include EC2 infrastructure - the hardware compute platform for running EC2 instances and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, or VPC, which enables customers to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud to launch their resources. The subnets, security groups, and network access control lists configured in the VPC are the responsibility of the customer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":true},{"id":"28aaf85b7ba1e63aa22c1c645a4c22e4","text":"Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) infrastructure","correct":true}]},{"id":"vikk5xb3-er5k-f530-xnql-upfbhr4zjhvv","domain":"concepts","question":"How many Availability Zones does each Region have?","explanation":"Normal Regions are made up of at least 2 Availability Zones to allow for highly available architectures in the cloud. The actual number of AZs can vary per Region.  There is a special class of Region called a 'Local Region' that have only 1 AZ, however that is viewed as an abnormal case by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"57ca7c66f61abc17eb42ff90f5bed87e","text":"At least 2","correct":true},{"id":"61f2018e5a51be7a751ae1eb61c1f017","text":"Regions don't have Availability Zones, Availability Zones have Regions","correct":false},{"id":"32cf9ef8a3f23b762138a410b9f02129","text":"Only 1","correct":false},{"id":"f3f74d2863be40169cddca9e902304f3","text":"At least 3","correct":false}]},{"id":"pdd3afvz-mr6t-zycv-zdle-ceeorrmdl4o9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program?","explanation":"Control Environment, Risk Management and Information Security are all components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program. Control Environment includes policies, processes and control activities that are in place to secure the delivery of AWS’ service offerings. AWS management has developed a strategic business plan which includes risk identification and the implementation of controls to mitigate or manage risks as part of the Risk Management component. AWS has implemented a formal information security program designed to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of customers’ systems and data.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/compliance/AWS_Risk_and_Compliance_Whitepaper.pdf","title":"AWS Risk and Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"7228bb53bb7855d458965d2f15fc6cd7","text":"Risk Management","correct":true},{"id":"0719bdee85b7a37d4e74a9d542d24861","text":" Physical Security","correct":false},{"id":"74f53be5e22fad65f914f82977df2447","text":"Control Environment","correct":true},{"id":"66216159eaf3a0abb2752836096f99e9","text":"Security Principles","correct":false},{"id":"0889f4cee1d9f42ae2c1daf686377de0","text":"Information Security","correct":true},{"id":"b8aba77333d3fc881739506fee08811c","text":"Environment Automation","correct":false}]},{"id":"gnnnfdzq-nbcz-7kwk-1vm0-oi8tdx8hjpg7","domain":"tech","question":"You need a “virtual hard disk” for your EC2 instance. Which of the following should you choose?","explanation":"EBS volumes are “virtual hard disks” for your EC2 instance.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ebs/","title":"About EBS"}],"answers":[{"id":"d02340dc3ba5e6755a60283779457ac6","text":"DDB","correct":false},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":true},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false}]},{"id":"e9686ec2-2edf-11ea-8a91-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are AWS Security, Identity, and Compliance services?","explanation":"KMS makes it easy to create and manage cryptographic keys, Secrets Manager protects the secrets you use for access to applications and services, and Security Hub consolidates your view of your security and compliance status in the cloud. AWS Organizations, which is the odd one out, is strictly concerned with management; you can use it to consolidate multiple AWS accounts into an organization that you create and centrally manage.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"b1820ee1cf68e2e65f263ff7bb207626","text":"AWS Organizations","correct":false},{"id":"03883d80013dc0b2b972eccd5b93b56f","text":"AWS Security Hub","correct":true},{"id":"7898cb92c418aeed6974ede9cb146462","text":"AWS Secrets Manager","correct":true},{"id":"d200c22f00ca54467dc4ad3823710388","text":"AWS Key Management Service (KMS)","correct":true}]},{"id":"04uew9ya-7pbn-ugmi-3vzh-1erxijop26v7","domain":"billing","question":"You are an AWS Enterprise customer with questions about billing and your overall AWS account. Which of the following AWS support personnel should you contact?","explanation":"For AWS Enterprise customers, the AWS Concierge is a resource dedicated to answering billing and account questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/features/","title":"AWS Support Features"}],"answers":[{"id":"bac90b5cd782c7dc092efa042af32e5c","text":"AWS Concierge","correct":true},{"id":"26e8220e8fac28d2a1a9a18ca81aabd7","text":"AWS Support","correct":false},{"id":"0037cad42801741c9acb59d7d7ba9a5f","text":"AWS Billing and Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"aebccaafe1827e1ed91b1d9a27dac4a8","text":"AWS Technical Account Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"b1acc5ea-cc62-4f91-9d0c-badb7c8ef957","domain":"tech","question":"You have been tasked with creating identical, repeatable Infrastructure for your customers. Which service will you use?","explanation":"CloudFormation provides the ability to provision a repeatedly deployable environment for your customers, CloudFront is a Content Delivery Network used to Cache content across the world. CloudWatch is used for telemetry and AWS Config is used to assess, audit and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"AWS Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"2d80a80d60fea86242f99512dbac7529","text":"AWS Config","correct":false},{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":true},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":false}]},{"id":"30rp7hn8-3uti-zql0-ays0-x3qfjnnnaax9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones?","explanation":"A Region is a geographic area that hosts two or more Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"0ed2343b7ec3f778399e20cf93f8f507","text":"Compute Zones","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true}]},{"id":"cpv9q14j-4nnf-wb3n-urul-qo85pzcs4lot","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following best describes a Resource Group?","explanation":"A resource group is a collection of resources that share one or more tags (or portions of tags.)","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsconsolehelpdocs/latest/gsg/what-are-resource-groups.html","title":"What Are Resource Groups?"}],"answers":[{"id":"dabdc344de93e3ccb3d5245b1f871f94","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources of the same type (EC2, S3, etc.) that are deployed in the same Availability Zone.","correct":false},{"id":"7ff9ffa66bb042afad45110ef6296a1a","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources that share one or more tags (or portions of tags.)","correct":true},{"id":"85a53afa2201152c277b7a584e2933be","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources that are deployed in the same Availability Zone.","correct":false},{"id":"02853c1436655d9187bb9d61a5b2ce70","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources of the same type (EC2, S3, etc.) that share one or more tags or portions of tags.","correct":false}]},{"id":"5ayciun1-a7hg-i7yq-4oeq-elwlon69tcex","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below terms represents a series of Edge Locations plus information about how you want content managed as part of a CDN?","explanation":"A Distribution is made up of Edge Locations that you want to serve content from, and details about how that content will be tracked an managed. Edge Groups and Circulations are not CloudFront Concepts, and although Load Balancer is an AWS service that helps you direct web traffic, it is not applicable in this case.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/distribution-working-with.html","title":"Working with Distributions"}],"answers":[{"id":"4e4e3ccc157ce52c9ddcf1d7277faf6e","text":"A Distribution","correct":true},{"id":"da8c85132b9bd45b3e8415405c753343","text":"A Circulation","correct":false},{"id":"59e3676a32b06a177d0617fde3d2ca48","text":"An Edge Group","correct":false},{"id":"c680109c8813a5a660a981f781dc0b1e","text":"A Load Balancer","correct":false}]},{"id":"cliqnjyx-pd1z-74c0-p0h5-gl8ufv76fo42","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are valid EC2 pricing options?","explanation":"On-Demand, where you pay for the resources you have used at the end of the billing period, and Reserved, were you commit to paying a certain amount every billing period for a length of time no matter if you used them or not, are the valid EC2 pricing options.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"4cc6684df7b4a92b1dec6fce3264fac8","text":"Global","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true}]},{"id":"6c02ad88-1feb-11ea-a32c-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon DynamoDB storage will you get?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 25 GB of DynamoDB storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"dcfebc6fbca2c5316f55c914e6593d2d","text":"100 GB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false},{"id":"272aa49fa956677af70625391009423f","text":"25 GB","correct":true},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false}]},{"id":"upv9n2ts-iwzj-4vez-gyls-rnpppswzz8zm","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below is true about root accounts on AWS?","explanation":"The root user has access to absolutely everything in an AWS account, and therefore should not be used for normal day to day activities and be reserved for when things go wrong. AWS will never ask you for any usernames or passwords as part of a support request  - so any request to do so should be treated with suspicion. The root user cannot be disabled.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"547527745e6b2e9620cf7400b9c03c91","text":"The root user has full access to everything in the AWS account","correct":true},{"id":"eb189b7195d97fe576a8babd440bd471","text":"The root user should not be used for day to day activities","correct":true},{"id":"3db3937d9b6115b761fee0d0a7ad9975","text":"The root user is the recommended way to work in the AWS Console","correct":false},{"id":"5c25f0724b86a34c79909772ae00ddd2","text":"The root user should be disabled after you create an Admin user","correct":false},{"id":"8d2e8228cfcd751c2f8d90fe0712a9f0","text":"The root user will be used by AWS should they need to help you with something in your account","correct":false}]},{"id":"a4a20c80-1512-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements are true of Amazon Aurora?","explanation":"Amazon Aurora is compatible with MySQL and PostgreSQL, and you can handle routine database tasks on it using either the AWS Management Console, AWS CLI commands, or API operations. As a relational database offering, it is part of the RDS service, not DynamoDB, which is AWS’s nonrelational database service. In addition, Aurora delivers up to five times the throughput of MySQL, not three times.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"87b549b9a5f186a6d978ec037b9d268f","text":"It uses the AWS Management Console, AWS CLI commands, and API operations to handle routine database tasks.","correct":true},{"id":"542b22f6c50dd511f8e64db1ac734bc6","text":"It is compatible with the MySQL and PostgreSQL database engines.","correct":true},{"id":"ca3a9ff8718b6a2ed0c56d839b5313b0","text":"It can deliver up to three times the throughput of MySQL.","correct":false},{"id":"16e59a8af37a34b9625d2d16558ef925","text":"It is part of the Amazon DynamoDB service.","correct":false}]},{"id":"bcecb806-dc3d-42d5-abaf-92b78f78bf00","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to network security for an EC2 instance in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service. In this scenario, AWS is responsible for the underlying network hardware, not the customer. However the customer is responsible for ensuring that only wanted, valid traffic reaches their EC2 instance through the use of Security Groups, Access Control Lists or Software Firewalls","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"e61949c2c6f3b07d6b052aeed05cafd5","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring unwanted traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"3bab15fdca03e0fc9fcb17e344d1ffed","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not impair the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"01407b8624848ffc3a63fcbb919421fb","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not impair the network hardware","correct":true},{"id":"d06119c27ec0a4e3b321bd66da22fea2","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"4aa6ca9653c0c4e24ff62399d1e4ca09","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"1dbd0eb41e4e90508191eb1f5a99b615","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring unwanted traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":true}]},{"id":"27ohq41k-k7qp-a4r2-2r7m-05za454l4hk3","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers 24x7 support via phone or chat?","explanation":"The Business and Enterprise support plans, the two most expensive plans, offer 24 X 7 support via phone or chat. Neither of the other support plans (Basic and Developer) offer Phone support. Individual is also not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]},{"id":"e5705f98-2edd-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following falls under the AWS database services category?","explanation":"ElastiCache, which serves as Amazon’s in-memory data store, is the only AWS database service listed here. The others are AWS storage services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"df346128c45efa43efc29607224fc716","text":"Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3)","correct":false},{"id":"d2a6652ddeb631da029d1f2806e11fdc","text":"Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)","correct":false},{"id":"770b120ec487568871cc9ab64475af46","text":"Amazon ElastiCache","correct":true},{"id":"4b21f5ceb7fb3f03f0d53a427f6be836","text":"Amazon FSx","correct":false}]},{"id":"fd097342-1bc8-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"CloudFront is used to route users to the edge location that provides the lowest amount of time delay in delivering content. Which of the following terms describes this 'time delay'?","explanation":"Latency refers to the amount of time delay during the processing of network data. CloudFront is AWS’s content delivery network service, which routes users to the edge location with the lowest latency. That means the content will be delivered as fast as possible.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/Introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon CloudFront?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e3cba4d3cce16ddf0ce129e981fb5bc2","text":"resiliency","correct":false},{"id":"aa3d4919f7245b97e2663e9bd2c15100","text":"elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"7883a7305bcbd394f768e04b9e800f53","text":"latency","correct":true},{"id":"314a0d25c2c847aaa07e42887fda1f7b","text":"scalability","correct":false}]},{"id":"b765b318-eee7-4587-a58c-299e41d2da84","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below allow you to restrict access to an entire S3 bucket? ","explanation":"Access Control Lists let you control access to individual objects within an S3 bucket, whereas Bucket Policies allow you to control access to entire buckets. In relation to S3, Bucket Control Lists and Access Policies do not exist as configuration items.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/using-iam-policies.html","title":"About S3 Bucket Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"7cfde5ee620a2532233ca18a68fd35ba","text":"Bucket Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"8eaf761b0344c54cfcf063cb006e4ad1","text":"Access Policies","correct":false},{"id":"5a804d2999d40df9fee58c79e96c4bc6","text":"Bucket Policies","correct":true},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef32cbf3-49b8-406a-aa2d-eaff05300839","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are separate from Regions and AZs. The number of Edge Locations around the world is greater than that of Regions and Availability Zones, in order to reduce latency between your content and your customers - the more that exist, the greater the chance there is one where you need it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"5810cb8fea9cc8e7773f9cc96fdd6c51","text":"There are more Regions than Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"b8ecf41dfa2a8f2d576a9407c87dadf5","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"9fe244cde3895fdb2a60650e6154c15b","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"78f3c24434277d629cc0a0d14f18c598","text":"There are more Edge locations than Availability zones","correct":true}]},{"id":"150e71c2-9b46-4a48-bed4-ef89f73570ae","domain":"tech","question":"Although you know that your Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) volumes are designed to be highly reliable, you want to further mitigate the possibility of a failure. Which of the following should you do?","explanation":"Backup of the EBS volumes can be created by taking point-in-time snapshots. These components are stored in S3. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/EBSSnapshots.html","title":"Amazon EBS Snapshots"},{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-building-fault-tolerant-applications.pdf?did=wp_card&trk=wp_card","title":"Fault-Tolerant Components on AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"e2f843acc6781a153857118f92da89f4","text":"Mitigating the possibility of a failure is not necessary.","correct":false},{"id":"2f63e74501f200b9859c7b5976101e79","text":"Make copies of the EBS volumes and store them in Amazon S3.","correct":false},{"id":"a2a7a68497095df080fb01033b2aea46","text":"Create backups of the EBS volumes in Amazon RDS.","correct":false},{"id":"44023459578ef9dc57780fc55ee56f7d","text":"Take snapshots of the EBS volumes.","correct":true}]}]}}}}
